The Wonderful Wizard Of Oz. I mean, I've always wanted to play the role of Dorothy.
《绿野仙踪》。我是说，我一直想扮演多萝西这个角色。
We are so not in Boulder right now.
我们现在绝对不在博尔德。
♪
- I was so close.
- 我差点就得手了。
You had the shoes in your hand
你手里拿着鞋子
and then like magic, they were gone.
然后就像魔法一样，它们消失了。
- It wasn't like magic. It was magic.
- 那不是像魔法，那就是魔法。
- She tricked you with lollipops.
- 她用棒棒糖骗了你。
- Magical lollipops. - And then she poofed herself.
- 神奇的棒棒糖。 - 然后她就消失了。
- How do you stop a poof?
- 你怎么阻止一个消失？
- You can only stop a poof with a poof.
- 你只能用一个poof来阻止一个poof。
- Oh, well then, can you poof?
- 哦，那么，你能poof吗？
- Sorry, I can only ding.
- 抱歉，我只能ding。
[bell dings]
[铃声ding]
- Dang. That's some ding.
- 该死。那个ding真厉害。
- I can't believe you guys.
- 真不敢相信你们。
Without the shoes, how am I supposed to
没有鞋子，我怎么证明我是真正的Dorothy。
prove that I'm the real Dorothy.
- 你不能，因为我才是。
- You can't, because I am.
- 不，我才是。
- No, I am.
- 只有一种方法能确定谁是真正的Dorothy。
- There's only one way to know for sure
- 只有一种方法能确定
who the real Dorothy is.
谁是真正的多萝西。
both: How? - Go ask the Wizard.
两人同时: 怎么做? - 去问巫师。
- Oh, of course, the Wizard. It's Oz, duh.
- 哦，当然，巫师。这是奥兹国，显然。
Hey, could you ding me there?
嘿，你能把我传送到那里吗？
- Sorry, I can only ding myself.
- 抱歉，我只能传送我自己。
You're going to have to follow the Orange Brick Road.
你得沿着橙色砖路走。
- Well then, I guess I'm going to see the Wizard.
- 那么，我想我得去见巫师了。
- You hear that, boys? We're gonna go see the Wizard.
- 你们听到了吗，伙计们？我们要去见巫师。
- I feel a song coming on. - I'm all oiled up.
- 我感觉要唱首歌了。 - 我已经准备好了。
And a one and a two--
一、二——
- Stop the music!
停下音乐！
No singing.
不许唱歌。
Here's the thing: I would rather do this on my own.
问题是：我宁愿自己来做这件事。
- [gasps] Alone? - Without us?
独自一人？
- I'm just saying, in light of 108 recent events.
没有我们？
- But only one in Oz.
我只是说，鉴于最近108起事件。
- I might have a better chance on my own.
但在奥兹国只有一次。
Now if you'll excuse me, I have to beat
我独自一人可能更有机会。
that fake Dorothy to the Wizard.
现在请原谅，我得赶在那个假多萝西之前见到巫师。
Wait, where is she?
等等，她在哪儿？
- Oh, just picking up these new shoes.
- 哦，只是去拿这些新鞋子。
You know, I never would have beat you to the Wizard in socks.
你知道，我光着脚袜子是绝不可能比你先到巫师那儿的。
[laughs]
[笑]
- Gotta go.
- 得走了。
- I'm starting to get the feeling
- 我开始有种感觉，
she doesn't want us to go with her anymore.
她不再想让我们跟着她了。
- It's because she doesn't. She doesn't trust us anymore.
- 那是因为她确实不想。她不再信任我们了。
- I wish there was some way we could regain her trust.
- 我希望有什么办法能重新赢得她的信任。
- We could if we helped prove she's the real Dorothy.
- 如果我们能证明她是真正的多萝西，我们就能。
- What if we got her shoes back?
- 如果我们帮她把鞋子拿回来呢？
- Good idea. You do have a brain!
- 好主意。你还真有点脑子！
- No, bad idea.
- 不，这是个坏主意。
The Wicked Witch has the shoes,
邪恶女巫有那双鞋子，
and she can poof.
而且她会瞬间移动。
I don't wanna get poofed.
我不想被她瞬间移动走。
- Relax, fur ball.
- 放松，毛球。
She can't poof what she can't see.
她看不见的东西，她就没法瞬间移动。
We'll sneak in.
我们可以悄悄潜入。
- Okay, but how are we gonna get there?
- 好吧，但我们怎么去那里呢？
- Maybe we can poof ourselves there.
也许我们可以瞬间移动过去。
- It's worth a shot.
值得一试。
One, two, three, poof!
一，二，三，瞬间移动！
[straining sound]
[用力声]
[popping]
[爆裂声]
My hat!
我的帽子！
[metal clangs]
[金属撞击声]
- All right, everybody spread out
好了，大家散开
and find his hat.
去找他的帽子。
♪ ♪
- Oh, no, Squishy. A fork in the road.
哦，不，squishy，路上有个岔口。
Wonder which is the way to the Wizard.
想知道哪条路通往巫师那里。
- Well, since you asked. - Ew!
既然你问了。
- This way's the shortest. - Perfect.
这边是最短的路线。
- Uh, but on the other hand,
太好了。
this way's the fastest.
但是另一方面，
- Great, thanks. - On the other hand,
这条路是最快的。
if you go that way, you have to walk on broken glass
太棒了，谢谢。
and might get trapped in a blizzard.
但另一方面，如果你走那条路，就得踩着碎玻璃走，还可能被困在暴风雪中。
Maybe take the other way.
或许还是选另一条路吧。
- Good advice. - Although,
it is a dangerous climb up a steep mountain.
- And how is that better?
- Well, it's better than running across broken glass
in a blizzard as you're getting eaten by tigers.
- Wait, blizzards and tigers? - And bears.
- No way. I'll go this way.
- Right. I totally would.
- But on the other hand-- - Ugh!
♪ ♪
- Are we sure this is the Witch's castle?
- 我们确定这是女巫的城堡吗？
- Yeah, look.
- 是的，看。
[both laugh]
[两人笑]
- I don't get it.
- 我不明白。
- Oh, you have to have a brain.
- 哦，你得有脑子。
Now we need to go in there and get those shoes for Dawn.
现在我们需要进去为Dawn拿那些鞋子。
- Right. Now stick to my plan. Ring the doorbell.
- 对。现在按照我的计划行事。按门铃。
- How come I have to ring the bell?
- 为什么我得按门铃？
Cowardly's my first name.
懦弱是我的名字。
- Because we beat you at rock paper scissors.
- 因为我们用石头剪刀布赢了你。
- I can only do paper with these paws.
- 我只能用这爪子出布。
- Just ring the doorbell.
- 快去按门铃。
- [growls]
- [低吼]
[man laughing maniacally]
- [男人疯狂地笑]
- Um, who's there?
- 呃，谁在那儿？
- Now wedge the rock in the doorway.
- 现在把石头塞在门缝里。
- Ugh!
- 呃！
[door creaking shut]
- [门吱吱作响地关上]
- Yes! I did it! I'm brave!
- 太好了！我做到了！我勇敢了！
High paw!
- 高爪击掌！
- Get 'em every time. - [laughs]
- But on the other hand-- - Okay, look, no more hands.
I'm sorry, Mr. Fork Man, but I'm just in a really big hurry.
- Which way to the Wizard? - On the one hand--
- You know what? You should stay and listen to this.
It's very informative. - Oh, no you don't!
[bell dings]
- You know, that way is the mountain
and that way is the tigers and broken glass.
- Huh.
♪ ♪
- You guys feel like we've been here before?
- 你们觉得我们好像来过这里？
[man screaming]
[男人尖叫]
- Pretty sure we would've remembered the screaming.
- 非常确定我们如果来过，会记得这尖叫声。
- Ooh, guys, look.
- 哦，伙计们，看。
An all-you-can-eat boiled egg bar.
一个无限量的煮蛋吧。
- Those aren't eggs, those are eyeballs.
- 那些不是鸡蛋，是眼球。
- Mm, who cares? The diet starts tomorrow.
- 嗯，谁在乎呢？节食从明天开始。
Mm, mm. - Oh, God.
嗯，嗯。 - 哦，天哪。
- Okay, focus. We need to find
- 好吧，集中注意力。我们需要找到
the sparkly, silver shoes.
那双闪亮的银色鞋子。
- There they are!
- 它们在那儿！
- I can't grab them.
- 我抓不到它们。
Those were just a hologram.
那些只是全息影像。
- But why would the Wicked Witch trick us
- 但为什么邪恶女巫要骗我们站在房间中央呢？
into standing in the middle of the room?
- 我的意思是，一定有某种原因。
[machinery clanking]
- 我完全搞不懂。
I mean, there must be some reason.
- [狞笑]
I'm stumped.
- [cackling]
Now, is there anything more exciting
现在，还有什么比邪恶计划变为现实更令人兴奋的呢？
than an evil plan coming to life?
囚犯们，飞天猴，还有那个家伙在干的事。
Prisoners, winged monkeys,
而我，是他们中最邪恶的那个。
whatever that guy's doing.
呜呼！
And me, the wickedest of them all.
哦，这真是个邪恶的整蛊。
Whee!
- 求求你，我们很抱歉。放我们走吧。
Oh, that's a wicked wedgie.
- 哎呀，你们哪儿也去不了。
- Please, we're sorry. Let us go.
[怪笑]
- Aww, you're not going anywhere.
[咳嗽]
[cackles]
[青蛙呱呱叫]
[coughs]
[咳嗽声]
[frog croaking]
[青蛙叫声]
I have a frog in my throat.
我喉咙里有只青蛙。
Always trying to get out. [frog croaking]
总是想逃出来。[青蛙叫声]
Get back in there, Frank!
快回去，弗兰克！
[swallows] - Uhh!
[吞咽声] - 呃！
♪ ♪
[roaring]
[咆哮声]
- [panting]
- [喘气声]
Oh, I need to see the Wizard
哦，我需要见巫师
to prove that I'm the real Dorothy.
以证明我是真正的多萝西。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
等等，等等，等等。
You can't just barge in here, expecting to see the Wizard.
你不能就这样闯进来，指望见到巫师。
there's a waiting list. - But this is really important.
这里有个等候名单。 - 但这真的很重要。
- Don't worry, I prioritized the list
别担心，我已经根据重要性优先处理了名单。 [门关闭]
based on importance. [door closes]
我需要和巫师谈谈。这非常重要。
- I need to speak to the Wizard. It's very important.
我找不到我的腰带了。
I can't find my belt.
名单上的第一位。
- Top of the list.
等等，但这怎么就更重要了？
- Wait, but how is that more important?
你知道吗？你可以先去。
You know what? You can go first.
But I am right after him.
但我紧随其后。
I need to see the Wizard before...
我需要在见到巫师之前...
- I need to see the Wizard to prove
- 我需要见巫师来证明
that I'm the real Dorothy.
我是真正的多萝西。
...That. - Two Dorothys?
...那个。 - 两个多萝西？
You can go in now. both: Really?
你现在可以进去了。
- No. Take a seat.
- 不。坐下。
- Hey, get off me! - And the chair talks!
- 嘿，放开我！ - 椅子还会说话！
It's all yours.
轮到你了。
♪ ♪
- [cackling]
- [怪笑]
- We've gotta get out of here.
- 我们得离开这儿。
- You're never getting out of here
- 你们休想离开这儿
- I'm a super villain and even I can't get out of here.
- 我是个超级反派，连我都出不去。
Word of warning, don't try to use her slide
给你个忠告，别未经允许就想玩她的滑梯。
without permission.
她可喜欢那个滑梯了。
She loves that slide.
我觉得她喜欢滑梯给屁股带来的感觉。
I think she likes the way it feels on her tushy.
我对你们三个有大计划。
- I've got big plans for you three.
当你们喝下这个，你们都会变成飞天猴！
When you drink this,
当你喝下这个，
you will all turn into winged monkeys!
你们都会变成带翅膀的猴子！
[coughs] [frog croaks]
[咳嗽声] [青蛙叫声]
- Ohh. - Not hungry.
- 哦。 - 不饿。
- Hard pass.
- 坚决拒绝。
- Hey, fur for brains, taste this.
- 嘿，毛脑袋，尝尝这个。
- What--what's in it for me?
- 我有什么好处？
- I don't make you soup.
- 我又没给你做汤。
- Soup's overrated.
- 汤太普通了。
- No, I think she meant she's going to make you into soup.
- 不，我想她的意思是她要把你做成汤。
- I know. I'm just stalling to extend my life.
我知道，我只是想拖延时间延长我的生命。
- Why do we have to play this game every time?
为什么我们每次都得玩这个游戏？
Just drink it, carrot breath!
快喝吧，胡萝卜味的！
- Better than frog breath.
总比青蛙味的好。
Fine.
好吧。
Mm, mm, mm. [suckling]
嗯，嗯，嗯。
Ahh.
啊。
Nothing happened.
什么都没发生。
Uh, ah, ohh, ew!
呃，啊，哦，哎呀！
Wow, do I have something on my back?
哇，我背上有什么东西吗？
- Yeah, super cute tiny wings.
是的，超级可爱的小翅膀。
What'd she say?
她说什么？
all: Super cute tiny wings.
超级可爱的小翅膀。
♪ ♪
- Next up, Dorothy v. Dorothy.
接下来，多萝西对多萝西。
- May the best Dorothy win. - Oh, you mean
愿最好的多萝西获胜。
the only Dorothy, me. - Uh, no. Me.
哦，你指的是唯一的多萝西，我。
- I'll be the judge of that!
呃，不。是我。
- It is I,
我会是那个评判的人！
the great Wizard of Oz.
是我，伟大的奥兹巫师。
Who dares ask me--
谁敢问我——
oh, hey, honey! - Wait, Dad?
哦，嘿，亲爱的！ - 等等，爸爸？
You're the Wizard? - Eh.
你是巫师？ - 嗯。
- Weird but sweet.
- 奇怪但温馨。
This is gonna be easy. - It's not just Dad.
这会很容易。 - 不只是爸爸。
We're co-wizards!
我们是联合巫师！
I told you not to start without me.
我告诉过你不要在我没到之前开始。
- And I told you we didn't have time to stop
- 我也告诉过我们没时间在小巫师的房间停留。
in the little wizard's room. - Oh!
- 哦！
- Okay, guys, guys, focus.
- 好了，伙计们，集中注意力。
Tell this fake Dorothy that I am the real Dorothy.
告诉这个冒牌的桃乐丝，我才是真正的桃乐丝。
- And what makes you think you're the real Dorothy?
- 你凭什么认为你是真正的桃乐丝？
- Ha, what do you mean? I'm Dorothy.
- 哈，你什么意思？我就是桃乐丝。
I mean, I have the hair and the dress.
我的意思是，我有头发和裙子。
- Uh, so do I!
- 呃，我也有！
- But I have the dog.
- 但我有狗。
[both gasp]
[两人惊讶]
- Oh, he is so cute! - [squeals]
- 哦，他太可爱了！
[both speaking gibberish] - Who's that little man?
[两人说着听不懂的话]
Who's that little man?
那个小男人是谁？
Well, this is a tough one.
嗯，这是个难题。
Give us one second!
给我们一点时间！
We have come to a decision.
我们已经做出决定了。
- Great. Who's the real Dorothy?
太好了。谁是真正的多萝西？
- No, not about that. About dinner.
不，不是那个。是关于晚餐。
We are ordering pizza!
我们要订披萨！
- I thought we decided on burgers.
我以为我们决定吃汉堡。
- One more second.
再等一下。
[bell dings] - Ahh!
叮！啊！
A little heads up next time.
下次提前通知一下。
- That's what the ding is for.
- 那叮的一声就是为此而设的。
Look, we have a problem.
看，我们有个问题。
- Hey, no fair. You can't get help from the Good Witch.
- 嘿，这不公平。你不能向好女巫求助。
- Can't you just freeze her? - We've been over this,
- 你就不能把她冻住吗？ - 我们之前讨论过这个，
I ding, that's all I do. I ding and I'm done.
我叮一声，这就是我全部的工作。我叮一声，然后就结束了。
Excuse us.
请原谅我们。
- Ooh. Don't mind me.
- 哦，别介意我。
I'll just be reading "Oz Weekly."
我就在这里读读《奥兹周刊》。
Ooh, looks like Selena Gomoz has a new lip gloss.
哦，看来赛琳娜·戈麦斯有新的唇彩了。
- Now look, your brothers are in trouble.
- 现在看看，你的兄弟们遇到麻烦了。
See for yourself on my "Good Witch Sees All" app.
你自己看我的“好巫婆无所不见”应用。
- Oh, hey, I've always wanted one of those.
哦，嘿，我一直想要一个那样的。
- Yeah, they're cool, but they eat up a lot of data.
是啊，它们很酷，但会消耗很多数据。
Anyway, the boys thought you'd have a better chance
总之，男孩们认为如果你穿着闪亮的银鞋出现
proving you're Dorothy if you showed up here
证明你是多萝西的机会会更大。
with the sparkly, silver shoes.
所以他们去了女巫的城堡去取鞋。
So they went to the Witch's castle to get them.
等等，真的吗？
- Wait, really?
他们为我做了这些？
They did that for me?
是的。但他们被抓住了。看。
- Yeah. But they got caught. Look.
哦，不。
- [cackling]
（咯咯笑）
- Oh, no.
哦，不。
- Hey, sorry to interrupt, but does anybody know
嘿，抱歉打断一下，但有人知道
a good sushi place?
一家价格合理的寿司店吗？
- That's reasonably priced!
你确定要吃便宜的寿司吗？
- Are you sure you want cheap sushi?
记得上次发生的事吗？
Remember what happened last time?
再等一分钟。
- One more minute. - Yeah.
我不想让邪恶女巫把我们变成带翅膀的猴子。
- I don't want the Wicked Witch to turn us into winged monkeys.
他们的翅膀甚至不管用。
Their wings don't even work.
带翅膀的猴子。那可不是好生活。
- Ooh, winged monkeys. That's not a good life.
哎呀，长翅膀的猴子。这生活可不好过。
- You should probably go save them.
你应该去救救他们。
- Okay, do you mind?
好吧，你介意吗？
This is a chips and cheese conversation.
这是吃薯片和奶酪的谈话。
As in, nachos. Queso, get out of my conversation.
比如，墨西哥玉米片。奶酪，别插嘴。
- Oh! What about Mexican? - Ah, no, we had it
哦！墨西哥菜怎么样？
for breakfast. - Queso?
啊，不行，我们早餐吃过了。
Uno momento.
奶酪？
- Okay, look, I feel bad for the boys,
等一下。
but I'm a dinner order away from being declared Dorothy.
好吧，听着，我为那些男孩感到难过，但我离被宣布成为多萝西只有一个晚餐订单的距离了。
- I bet if Dawn knew where we were,
我打赌如果Dawn知道我们在哪儿，
she'd come save us.
她会来救我们的。
- Of course she would.
当然她会的。
- Mm-hmm. Who's letting who down now?
嗯哼。现在是谁让谁失望了？
- Ooh!
哦！
- You know what? You need to think about this.
你知道吗？你需要好好想想。
I'm gonna leave you alone,
我要让你一个人待会儿，
possibly with your own spotlight
可能还会给你打上聚光灯
and a little background music.
和一点背景音乐。
- Don't worry, Dawn will save us.
别担心，Dawn会救我们的。
- She'd never give up on us.
- 她永远不会放弃我们。
Just like we'd never give up on her.
- 就像我们永远不会放弃她。
- ♪ Comes a time when you have to make a choice ♪
- ♪ 总有一个时刻，你必须做出选择 ♪
♪ Feelings that you probably should have voiced ♪
♪ 那些你本该表达的情感 ♪
♪ They'll be fine this is my dream ♪
♪ 他们会没事的，这是我的梦想 ♪
♪ Understand, 'cause I'll be Dorothy ♪
♪ 理解吧，因为我会成为多萝西 ♪
♪ Finally, I get to be the lucky girl ♪
♪ 终于，我成了那个幸运的女孩 ♪
♪ But why does it feel like I'm alone in this world? ♪
♪ 但为什么我感觉自己在这个世界孤身一人？ ♪
- ♪ Should we get some barbecue? ♪
- ♪ 我们应该吃点烧烤吗？ ♪
- ♪ No, I think barbecue is wrong ♪
- ♪ 不，我觉得烧烤不对 ♪
- ♪ Should we get some nice soup? ♪
♪ 我们应该来点美味的汤吗？ ♪
- ♪ I think she wants to get back to the song ♪
♪ 我觉得她想回到歌里 ♪
- ♪ I could breathe fire, walk through a storm ♪
♪ 我能喷火，穿越风暴 ♪
♪ I could be the player that hits the home run ♪
♪ 我可以成为那个击出全垒打的球员 ♪
♪ It could be amazing, but we could do better ♪
♪ 这可能很棒，但我们能做得更好 ♪
♪ Together, together, together, together ♪
♪ 一起，一起，一起，一起 ♪
♪ And stars will always shine bright ♪
♪ 星星将永远闪耀 ♪
♪ I'm stronger with those guys by my side ♪
♪ 有那些家伙在我身边，我会更强大 ♪
♪ I have to stand up for the things I believe ♪
♪ 我必须为我所相信的事情站出来 ♪
♪ Even if it means I might not be Dorothy ♪
♪ 即使这意味着我可能不再是多萝西 ♪
♪ Fire, walk through the storm ♪
♪ 火焰，穿越风暴 ♪
♪ I could be the player that hits the home run ♪
♪ 我可以成为那个击出全垒打的球员 ♪
♪ I have to stand up for the things I believe ♪
♪ 我必须为我所相信的事情站出来 ♪
♪ Even if it means I might not be Dorothy ♪
♪ 即使这意味着我可能不再是多萝西 ♪
- We've reached a decision!
我们已经做出了决定！
- Chinese!
中文！
Now back to this Dorothy question.
现在回到这个多萝西的问题上。
- Finally!
终于！
- Look, I've reached a decision, too.
看，我也做出了决定。
I have to go. - Wait, if she leaves
我必须走了。 - 等等，如果她离开
that makes me Dorothy, right?
那我就是多萝西了，对吧？
- Look, it's all yours, Dorothy.
看，这都是你的了，多萝西。
I have something way more important to do.
我有更重要的事情要做。
- So, Chinese, huh?
所以，中国人，是吗？
What restaurant?
哪家餐厅？
- One second!
等一下！
♪ ♪
- This is taking a long time to thicken,
这需要很长时间才能变稠，
but it's almost ready. [cackles]
但快好了。[咯咯笑]
- This mannequin looks weird.
这个假人看起来很奇怪。
That's better.
这样好多了。
- That witch mannequin is coming toward us!
- 那个女巫模特正朝我们走来！
- Which mannequin? - Yes.
- 哪个模特？ - 是的。
- No, which mannequin is coming towards us?
- 不，哪个模特正朝我们走来？
- That's what I'm saying.
- 我就是这个意思。
- It's me, Dawn. - Whoa!
- 是我，Dawn。 - 哇！
- Witch mannequin is Dawn.
- 女巫模特是Dawn。
- The one that just said, "It's me, Dawn."
- 就是刚才说“是我，Dawn”的那个。
- Come on, guys. It's time to get out of here.
- 快点，伙计们。是时候离开这里了。
- Yes!
- 是的！
- Not good!
不好！
This, also not good.
这个，也不好。
- What's not good about it?
有什么不好的？
Now I get to turn all four of you into winged monkeys.
现在我要把你们四个都变成飞天猴。
Now, drink up, my quaddies.
来吧，我的四胞胎们，喝吧。
And then you'll become pretty ugly.
然后你们就会变得非常丑陋。
Ha! You see what I did there?
哈！你们看到我刚做的了吗？
- Ha, you're so funny. - Hysterical.
哈，你真有趣。
- You should give up witching and go into stand-up.
太好笑了。
- Really?
你应该放弃做女巫，去说单口相声。
Wanna hear a joke?
想听个笑话吗？
- Sure.
当然。
- Who escapes the Witch's castle?
谁逃出了女巫的城堡？
- I don't know. Who?
我不知道。谁？
- Nobody.
没人。
Now drink the potion! - Ahh!
现在喝下这药水！
- Please tell me this wasn't your whole plan.
请告诉我这不是你全部的计划。
- It wasn't. Squishy!
不是的。Squishy！
[whistles]
（吹口哨）
[barking]
（吠叫）
[barking] - Ahh!
[吠叫声] - 啊！
- Yes! - We're saved!
- 是的！ - 我们得救了！
- You did it! - [cackles]
- 你做到了！ - [咯咯笑]
- Or you made things much, much worse.
- 或者你把事情搞得更糟了。
- Which is usually our thing.
- 这通常是我们的风格。
- How does it feel? - Not great.
- 感觉如何？ - 不太好。
- [cackles]
- [咯咯笑]
♪ ♪
- Okay, kids. Playtime's over.
- 好了，孩子们。游戏时间结束了。
- What are you going to do to us?
- 你要对我们做什么？
- I'm gonna show you just how wicked I am!
- 我要让你们见识见识我有多邪恶！
♪ ♪
- No, no, no, no, no music. No.
- 不，不，不，不，不许放音乐。不行。
[sighs] Look, you can sing until you're blue in the face.
[叹气]听着，你就算唱到脸都发青了。
Then I don't care if you turn us into winged monkeys.
我不在乎你是否把我们变成飞猴。
As long as you turn us into winged monkeys together.
只要我们一起变成飞猴就行。
So put that into a song and sing it.
所以把这写进歌里唱出来吧。
- Don't mind if I do.
- 那我就不客气了。
[frog croaking]
[青蛙叫声]
- How did you do that? - I didn't.
- 你怎么做到的？ - 我没做。
- Then who did? - Who cares? Run.
- 那会是谁？ - 谁在乎？快跑。
[frog croaking]
[青蛙叫声]
- What did you do to me? [croaks]
- 你对我做了什么？ [呱呱叫]
- They didn't do it.
他们没做。
We did!
是我们做的！
[croaking]
[呱呱叫]
- The great Wizards of Oz.
- 伟大的奥兹巫师。
all: What? - Um, sorry.
所有人：什么？ - 嗯，抱歉。
both: Mmm, mmm, mmm.
两人：嗯，嗯，嗯。
The great Wizards of Oz--
伟大的奥兹巫师--
this is so good.
这太好吃了。
Why did we ever stop going to Buddoz Belly?
我们为什么不再去Buddoz Belly了呢？
- Oh, because Pandoz Express opened.
哦，因为Pandoz Express开业了。
- Oh, right. [frog croaks]
哦，对了。[青蛙叫声]
Anyway, we've come to a decision on who the real Dorothy is.
总之，我们已经决定谁才是真正的多萝西了。
- Wait, but I thought when I left,
等等，但我以为我离开后，
Rose Dirken automatically got it.
Rose Dirken就自动获得了这个角色。
- Oh, that's what she said. - [laughs]
哦，她是这么说的。- [笑]
- But not what we said.
但那不是我们说的。
- Though some people may think that it's the hair
虽然有些人可能认为，是发型、裙子和鞋子造就了多萝西。
and the dress and the shoes that make the Dorothy.
还有那裙子和鞋子构成了多萝西的形象。
But the truth is, it's your actions
但事实上，是你的行为
that make you who you are.
决定了你是谁。
By saving your brothers, you acted like a true Dorothy.
通过拯救你的兄弟们，你展现了真正的多萝西精神。
- Wait, I did? [bell dings]
- 等等，我做到了吗？
- I knew you'd do the right thing.
- 我就知道你会做出正确的选择。
- Then it's settled. You're the real Dorothy.
- 那么就这么定了。你就是真正的多萝西。
- Here you go. You said to get extra chopsticks,
- 给你。你说要拿额外的筷子，
and then when I came out, you were gone, so--
然后我出来时，你已经不在了，所以——
What'd I miss?
我错过了什么？
all: She's the real Dorothy.
大家：她才是真正的多萝西。
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
- 哦，不，不，不，不，不。
You said I was the real Dorothy.
你说我是真正的多萝西。
- No, no, it's okay, Rose Dirken.
- 不，不，没关系，罗斯·迪肯。
You can be Dorothy.
你可以成为多萝西。
I just really wanna go home with my brothers
我只是真的很想和我的兄弟们、我的狗以及他们为我做的鞋子一起回家。
and my dog and the shoes they made for me.
- 如果你想回家，你知道该怎么做。
- If you want to go home, you know what to do.
- 是的，我知道。[笑]
- Yes, I do. [laughs]
- 哦，对不起。我不是在跟你说话。
- Oh, sorry. I wasn't talking to you.
这是我的幸运。[笑]
It's my fortune. [laughs]
这是我的财富。[笑]
But you know what to do.
但你知道该怎么做。
- There really is no place like...
- 真的没有地方像…
all: Careful.
大家小心。
- ...Home.
- …家。
Take me back to Boulder.
带我回博尔德。
[shimmering tone]
[闪烁的音调]
- Dawn, sweetie?
- 道恩，亲爱的？
- She's awake. Hey, kiddo, come on.
- 她醒了。嘿，孩子，过来。
- Oh, wait, what happened? - Uh, you were hit in the head
- 哦，等等，发生了什么？ - 呃，你被一个精心制作的舞台龙卷风击中了头部
by a skillfully crafted stage tornado.
被一个精心制作的舞台龙卷风击中。
- Ah-- - Okay, my dumb prop
- 啊-- - 好吧，我的愚蠢道具
made you hit your noggin.
让你撞到了头。
- But I was just in Oz.
- 但我刚刚在奥兹国。
- Oz? Dawn, you didn't go anywhere.
- 奥兹？Dawn，你哪儿也没去。
- No, I did, I was in Oz and there was an Orange Brick Road
- 不，我去了，我在奥兹国，那里有一条橙色砖路
and a weird fork man and I was that mannequin.
和一个奇怪的分叉人，我就是那个人偶。
- Wait, which mannequin?
- 等等，哪个玩偶？
- Exactly, so it was real.
- 没错，所以那是真实的。
- Uhh, okay.
- 呃，好吧。
- Look, I owe you guys an apology.
- 听着，我欠你们一个道歉。
I know you mess up sometimes
我知道你们有时会搞砸
and get in my way and make things really hard for me.
还会挡我的路，让我事情变得很困难。
- Are you sure this is an apology?
- 你确定这是道歉吗？
- But I do know that you always have my best interests in mind.
- 但我确实知道你们总是为我着想。
And in courage, and in heart.
在勇气上，在心意上。
- We have your best interests in heart?
- 你们把我的利益放在心上？
- That makes no sense. But I'll let it go,
- 这说不通。不过我会放过的，
since you're obviously concussed.
既然你显然是脑震荡了。
- And I also owe you an apology.
- 我也欠你一个道歉。
The only one who ruined my audition was me.
毁了我试镜的只有我自己。
I was just so focused on looking like Dorothy on the outside
我只是太专注于外表看起来像多萝西，
that I didn't act like Dorothy on the inside.
以至于内心没有表现出多萝西的样子。
So I'm sorry.
所以我很抱歉。
- I forgive you.
- 我原谅你。
- Air hug? - How about a real one? Hm?
- 空气拥抱？ - 来个真的怎么样？嗯？
[both laugh]
[两人笑]
Uh, hello, Rose Dirken, still stuck under a house!
呃，你好，罗斯·迪肯，还卡在房子下面！
- Lift it up.
- 把它抬起来。
- Okay, Rose. I just wanted to say
- 好的，罗斯。我只是想说
even though I really wanted the part,
即使我真的很想得到那个角色，
you totally deserve to be cast as Dorothy.
你完全应该被选为多萝西。
- Uh, duh! After all, I am the one
- 呃，当然！毕竟，我是那个
wearing Ericka's sparkly, silver shoes.
穿着埃里卡的闪亮银鞋的人。
[cracking] Ow! Wha! Ooh!
[咔嚓声] 哎哟！哇！哦！
Don't worry. I am okay.
别担心。我没事。
- Yeah, that girl's going down.
- 是的，那个女孩要倒下了。
- Ahh! [all gasp]
- 啊！[所有人都惊呼]
Ow, my ankle.
哎哟，我的脚踝。
- All right, Dawn. Looks like you're Dorothy.
- 好吧，道恩。看来你是多萝西了。
- Yes!
是的！
I mean, anything for the show.
我的意思是，为了节目，什么都行。
♪ ♪